AKPAN, VICTORIA DAVID

Front-end Web Developer

Phone: +2347087040050 | Email: veedahv55@gmail.com | GitHub: github.com/veedahv | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/victoria-akpan | Twitter: https://twitter.com/veedahv | Website: veedahv.me

PROFILE

I am a front-end web developer who specializes in creating fast and accessible websites. I reproduce replicas of designs using appropriate front-end technologies. I have experience working with and possess good knowledge of the following:

SKILLS - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, VueJS, Bootstrap, git

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Intern - Ustacky

December 2020 - till date

- I implemented designs using web technologies like HTML, CSS JavaScript, VueJs, Bootstrap.
- I mentor students and help students where they need help.

Code Reviewer - Ustacky

December 2020 - till date

• I review students' code and provide valuable feedback and advice.

EDUCATION

Front-End Micro-degree - Ustacky

December 2020 - till date

• I implemented an e-commerce website design integrated with Paystack test payment method.

Web Development - The Roothub

August - October 2020

- Created a shopping list app.
- Created a weather app.
- Created an e-commerce dashboard for an online store.

Front-End Development - FrontEndFoxes

April - June 2021

- Built a Bank App.
- Built a Typing Game.
- Built a Personal Portfolio webpage.
- Built a Pet App.
- Built a Browser Extension.

Computer Engineering – University of Uyo

Sep 2017 - Till date

• Built a simple airline booking platform

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer – GiveCampMemphis

February 2021

• I helped rebuild the mobile view of The Women Advocacy Center Site.

AWARDS

• Finalist at the Enye hackathon(2020)